

Zidane MOHAMED

Web and software developer

PROFILE

Computer science student with big dreams, I decide to make software engineering and web development like my passion. With my +2 years of experiences, I always wish to improve my skills with new challenges to achieve my goals!



+216 51 81 40 58 +225 07 79 26 16 19



madazada0@gnail.com



Tunis, TUNISIA



https://portfoliopersonnal.vercel.app/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/zid ane-mohamed-8a54561b2/

EDUCATION

2nd year Data Science engineer | 2022 **TEK-UP University** Ariana - Tunisie

Bachelor Web Technology | 2021 **ESATIC** Abidjan – Côte d'Ivoire

LANGUAGES

French: Fluent

English: Professional

SKILLS

- Drafting document's projects
- Project management
- Securing web applications
- Knowledge of graphic element

- MEAN Stack
- Laravel, PHP
- DevOps
- • • •
- Scripting
 - (python, java, c,

bash, shell)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

From 04/2022 Until Today

Software engineering consultant

Total Digital Service SARL | Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

- ${\bf Completed\ tasks:}$
 - Design & Realization of applications (web and mobile);
 - Design & creation of showcase websites;
 - Drafting of project documents.

From 06/20/2022 Until 09/28/2022

Development Intern – web security

Upgradetek Engineering | Ariana, Tunisie

Completed tasks:

- Web security solution integration;
- Creation of project documents (report, documentation);
- API and web interface development.

From 12/2020 Until 08/2022

Software engineer (Freelance)

Dr Digit | new Brunswick, Canada

Completed tasks:

- Mission 1: Design & creation of a showcase website for volunteering;
- Mission 2: Design & implementation of a car rental platform;
- Mission 3: Design & implementation of a ticket generation application (show, etc.);
- Mission 4: Advice on the development of an e-commerce platform;
- Mission 5: Design & implementation of a platform for creating a show and selling tickets.

From 08/2020 Until 08/2021

Web developer (work-linked training)

La Locomotive SARL | Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

Completed tasks:

- Design & implementation of integrated management software;
- Web design;
- Drafting of project documents.